quickarticlepro.com 2008-12-17

# Article Writing Software- Article Builder to write Informative Articles

|   
---  
  
|  |  |  |   
---|---|---  
At Quick Article Pro, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.   
|  | What information do we collect? How do we use it?   
---|---  
All of our sites are connected to one database. Your user profile only has to be established and/or edited at one location. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web sites. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. Our sites registration forms require users to give us contact information (like their name and E-mail address). We use customer contact information from the registration forms to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Our sites use forms for customers to request information, products, services, and support. We collect visitor information (like their account or credit card numbers).  
If you are purchasing something from Quick Article Pro, any third party provider, and we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. This allows us, or third party providers, to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. This information is used to send the invoice to you for products and services you purchase.  
|  | How does Quick Article Pro protect customer information?  
---|---  
Our sites have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our servers are certified for use with secured access for data transferred involving payment methods and sensitive information. The sites use SSL 128-bit encryption when accepting and transferring visitor provided information.   
|  | What are Cookies?   
---|---  
"Cookies" are small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes such as personalizing your user experience. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to keep a track of your shopping cart and to avoid showing same advertisements. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.  
|  | Will Quick Article Pro disclose the information it collects to outside parties?  
---|---  
Quick Article Pro does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy service partners but you can tell us not to by sending a blank e-mail message to support@quickarticlepro.com. Also, Quick Article Pro may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.  
|  | Contact us  
---|---  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our sites, or your dealings with our Web sites, you can contact:

E-mail: [support@quickarticlepro.com](mailto:support@quickarticlepro.com)  
  
|  |  |    
---|---|---  
Copyright 2008 Quick Article Softwares. All rights reserved
